让我们从一些知识开始。
Let's start with a bit of knowledge.
我们谈谈弦吧
Let's talk about strings.
字符串有什么有趣的地方 ?
What is something
interesting about strings?
有什么有趣的事吗
Anything interesting at all?
>> 它们是基本类型。
&gt;&gt; They're primitive type.
> > 嗯，它们是原始类型的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, they're primitive type, yeah.
这也是骗人的，因为 JavaScript 喜欢忽悠你。
Which is also deceiving because
JavaScript likes to trick you.
这是一种原始类型但
It's a primitive type, but
还有一些方法在我可以调用的字符串上。
there is also methods that
are on a string that I can call.
事实上，这些是一些有用的字符串方法。
In fact, these are some useful methods for
strings.
分割非常有用，因为使用分割可以将字符串转换为数组，并且
Split is useful because using split I
can turn a string into an array, and
一旦我有了阵列我就可以为所欲为了
then once I have the array I
can do whatever I want with it.
LowerCase 如果你要处理大量的字符串
LowerCase if you're dealing
with a lot of strings,
如果你在比较字符串的情况下要把它们都用小写字母
having to putting them all in
lowercase if you're comparing strings,
那样的话就没什么用了
things like that, just so
useful nothing, no.
子串或子 STR，具体取决于您希望用于获取部分
Substring or sub STR, depending which
one you like to use to get a part of
一个字符串从另一个字符串中开始，并且开头是惊人的。
a string out of another string and
starts with is amazing.
这不是几年前的问题了
It wasn't around to a couple of years ago.
在过去的时候也许正则表达式和所有这些东西的开头都是
In the old days, maybe regular expressions
and all this stuff starts with is so
最棒的结局
great ends with this.
有一些有用的方法也许我想说的是关于弦的事情
There's such useful methods, probably the
main thing I'd say to know about strings,
这些字符串是不可改变的
the strings are immutable.
一旦创建字符串，就无法更改它。
Once you create a string,
you can't change it.
如果你改变了它，你实际上是在创造另一个字符串。
And if you do change it,
you're actually creating another string.
重要的是要知道如果你缺少太多的字符串
And it's important to know that if
you're missing a lot of strings,
你只是在创造更多的字符串
you're actually just creating more and
more strings.
所以如果你看图表，如果你在做一个记忆档案，你会看到
So if you watch the graph, if you're
doing a memory profile, you'll see
如果你创造了大量的字符串，那么这个园丁会向上，向下，向上和向下。
the garselecter go up and down, and up and
down if you're creating a lot of strings.
通常，将字符串转换为数组，然后对其进行处理
Generally, it's useful to turn a string
into an array and then manipulate it and
将它返回到字符串中而不是创建串字符串。
turn it back into a string rather
than creating a bunch of strings.